

MATEO SAUTON

Phone Number: +54 911 53337487

E-mail: sautonmateo@gmail.com

Age: 25

CHIEF TECHNOLOGY OFFICER& TELECOMUNICATIONS ENGINEERING

PROFILE

Telecommunications Engineer. I am an international robot sumo fighter for ARTech robotics team with great experience in embedded systems. Moreover, I am part of Open Space winner team (TIAB) where we build Digital Twins for nano-satellites.

EXPERIENCE

CTO

n1u (2023 - Present)

- Scalable & Secure fintech solution
- Interdisciplinary User/Product focused team management

PRODUCT MANAGER

Agrotoken (2021 - 2023)

- Algorand/Ethereum/Polygon Blockchain PM
- Lead proyect manager for Stablecoin application
- Wallet App and Credit card PM

RPA SENIOR ENGINEER

Everis (2019 - 2021)

- Automation Anywhere Master Professional Certification (RPA)
- Agile and Scrum methodologies.

TEACHER ASISTANT

Universidad Nacional de San Martin (2018 - 2021)

• TA at Informatics course for engineers. C programming on Ubuntu 18.4 base environment.

APTITUDES -

- Machine Learning with Python: libraries such as (Pandas, Keras, Numpy, SKLearn, Scipy)
- C: Microcontroler programming for autonomus robots.
- Relational DB (SQL)
- DEV OPS: GNU/Linux, Docker, Ansible.

EDUCATION

TELECOMUNICATIONS ENGINEERING Universidad Nacional de San Martin (2016 - 2023)

SECONDARY BILINGUAL

Colegio Bede's Grammar School (2015)

EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES

REFORGE - Product Management - Finding PMF